Guide to the Rice University Art Gallery records, 1971-2017 UA 066
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XII: Digital content from compact discs
  - Exhibit videos (Folder "2001-2002")
  - Exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Fort Discomfort exhibit documents (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Tara Donovan's Haze exhibit poster and interview (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Fort Discomfort exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Tara Donovan exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Fort Discomfort exhibit photos, other documents (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey Dilston Grove exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey promotional photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey promotional photos and documents (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey promotional photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - 2004 student show promotional material (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Liang Wu painting images (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey exhibit photos (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey promotional materials (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Ackroyd & Harvey "Green brick, green back" exhibit description (Folder "2003-2004")
  - Alyson Shotz bio and photos of artwork (Folder "2003-2004")
  - 2004 Homecoming presentation (Folder "2004-2005")
  - Various photos (Folder "2004-2005")
  - Various photos (Folder "2004-2005")
  - Various photos (Folder "2004-2005")
  - Various photos (Folder "2004-2005")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation video (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation diagrams (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos, other architectural images (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos, other images (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos, other images (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos, other images (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban architectural drawings (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation photos, other images (Folder "Ban")
  - Shigeru Ban Bamboo Roof installation panels (Folder "Ban")
  - Bill Camfield photos, letters on his retirement (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Various documents (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Interactive art pieces (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Exhibit photos (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Exhibit photos (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Exhibit photos (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Various documents (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Various documents (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Student show documents (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Various documents (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Texas Association of Museums members invitation (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Bill Camfield photos (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Malcolm Gillis talk slideshow (Folder Unlabeled)
  - RAG slideshow (Folder Unlabeled)
  - Jaye Anderton images from Gillis Service Award and Rice going away party, 2011-2012
- Series XIII: Rice Gallery installation videos by Walley Films
  - Fall 2000 - Spring 2001
    - Martha Burgess: Manly on the Plaid, installation video by Walley Films, 2000
  - Fall 2002 - Spring 2003
    - Phoebe Washburn: True, False, and Slightly Better, 2010
  - Fall 2005 - Spring 2006
    - David Ellis: Bound and Conversation, installation video by Walley Films, 2007
    - Diane Landry: Flying School, Mandala Naya, and The Cod, installation video by Walley Films, 2017
  - Fall 2006 - Spring 2007
    - Judy Pfaff: ...all of the above, opening talk, installation video by Walley Film, 2007
  - Fall 2007 - Spring 2008
    - Charlie Roberts: MAMBO JAMBO: Cabinet of the Cosmos, excerpts from gallery talk, installation video by Walley Films, 2008
    - Kirsten Hassenfeld: Dans la Lune opening talks, installation video by Walley Films
    - Mark Fox: Dust, video interview by Walley Films, 2008
  - Fall 2008 - Spring 2009
    - Aurora Robson: The Great Indoors opening talk, installation video by Walley Films, and The Inner Life of a Cell video, 2010
    - Henrique Oliveira: Tapumes talks and installation video by Walley Films, 2009
    - Michael Salter: too much, installation and interview videos by Walley Films, 2008
    - Paul Villinski: Emergency Response Studio, video interview by Walley Films, 2009
  - Fall 2009 - Spring 2010
    - Andrea Dezso: Sometimes In My Dreams I Fly, installation video by Walley Films, 2010
    - El Anatsui: Gli (Wall), installation video by Walley Films, 2010
    - Wayne White: Big Lectric Fan to Keep Me Cool While I Sleep, installation video by Walley Films, 2009
  - Fall 2010 - Spring 2011
    - Mary Temple: Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, installation video by Walley Films, 2011
    - Sarah Oppenheimer: D-17, installation video by Walley Films, 2010
  - Fall 2011 - Spring 2012
    - Ana Serrano: Salon of Beauty, installation video by Walley Films, 2011
    - Joel Shapiro: Untitled, installation video by Walley Films, 2012
    - Yasuaki Onishi: reverse of volume RG, installation video by Walley Films, 2012
  - Fall 2012 - Spring 2013
    - Gunilla Klingberg: Wheel of Everyday Life, installation video by Walley Films, 2013
    - Soo Sunny Park: Unwoven Light, installation video by Waller Films, 2013
  - Fall 2013 - Spring 2014
    - Dinh Q. Lê: Crossing the Farther Shore, installation video by Walley Films, 2014
    - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, installation video by Walley Films, 2014
    - Gaia: MARSHLAND, installation video by Walley Films, 2013
  - Fall 2014 - Spring 2015
    - Atelier Bow-Wow: SHOTGUN, installation video by Waller Films, 2015
    - Ben Butler: Unbounded, installation video by Waller Films, 2015
    - Yusuke Asai: yamatane, installation video by Waller Films, 2014
  - Fall 2015 - Spring 2016
    - Anila Quayyum Agha: Intersections, installation video by Walley Films, 2015
    - Michael de Feo: Crosstown Traffic, installation video by Walley Films, 2016
    - Thorsten Brinkmann: The Great Cape Rinderhorn, installation video by Walley Films, 2016
  - Fall 2016 - Spring 2017
    - Jonathan Schipper: Cubicle, installation video by Walley Films, 2016